

CONTACT



+33 (6) 33 83 65 53



gueram.hov@proton.me



github.com/GeramHov



477, rue Dr Calmette, 42153 Riorges

SKILLS

- Team Work
- Organization
- Leadership
- Verbal & Written

LANGUAGE

French B2

English B2

• Russian C1

Armenian C2

GUERAM HOVHANNISYAN

TRAINING OF WEB DEVELOPER / WEB MOBILE

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I'm 31 years old Junior Web Developer currently studying at CCI Formation in Roanne, France. I enjoy the coding a lot and I'm working on myself to become an accomplished programmer in order to contribute my skills to the exciting technological advances that happen every day. I'm a former car mechanic and car electrician, converted to Web Development in late 2022.

WORK EXPERIENCE

MANAGING DIRECTOR I 01/2016 - 06/2022

"Alpha Garage" - Saint-Léger-sur-Roanne, France

- Car mechanic / electricity
- Workshop supervisor
- Administrative management
- Purchase / Sell / Repair / Car restoration renovation

SORTER, DELIVERY MAN I 08/2012 - 07/2014

"Le Tri d'Emma" - Villerest, France

- Packaging before delivery
- Sorting out (finished products, materials, parts..)

EDUCATION

CCI Formation Lyon - Saint Étienne - Roanne November 2022 - November 2023

Training of web development / web mobile / applications

GRETA du Roannais - Lycée Carnot - Roanne | Youth Training September 2014 - May 2015

Mechanics and maintenance of motor vehicles

Armenian State University of Economics - Yerevan | A-Levels September 2010 - October 2010

Accounting and auditing faculty

ETC - English and Exam Training Center - Yerevan September 2008 - June 2009

Training and Practicing in English

PhysMath School - Yerevan September 2008 - June 2009

Complementary training in mathematics before entering university